<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Edward Joesoef</title><link>https://edwardjoesoef.com/</link><description>Recent content on Edward Joesoef</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 22:17:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://edwardjoesoef.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Yet Another Beginnining</title><link>https://edwardjoesoef.com/logs/yet-another-beginnining/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 22:17:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://edwardjoesoef.com/logs/yet-another-beginnining/</guid><description>&lt;p>This isn’t the first time I’ve revived my own domain, and I’m sure there will be many more in the future. But I’m really hoping this one lasts longer than my past attempts.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For now, I plan to use this platform as my personal blog to keep track of things I’m doing to grow and pursue my passions. I hope I have more time to do this time around!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Stay tuned and thanks for visiting!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Edward Blog</title><link>https://edwardjoesoef.com/projects/edward-blog/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 06:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://edwardjoesoef.com/projects/edward-blog/</guid><description>&lt;p>This entire website represents my inaugural project, which I embarked upon after a prolonged hiatus due to unforeseen circumstances that arose during my professional and personal life.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Initially, my objective was to design the website with simplicity in mind, prioritizing ease of maintenance. I intend to implement incremental improvements periodically, adhering to the principles of agile development.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Story So Far ...</title><link>https://edwardjoesoef.com/me/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://edwardjoesoef.com/me/</guid><description>&lt;p>My name is Edward, and I am a data engineer at the TRUST Project in Singapore, a national platform dedicated to facilitating anonymized health data research and access to improve health outcomes. Before my current role, I gained valuable experience as a system analyst with TRUST and as a data analyst for a local fintech startup.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I am enthusiastic about learning new things and aspire to explore the application of technology across various fields. Like many, I am delving into AI applications, aiming to develop innovative projects to share on this blog.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>